[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
THAT DOCTOR IS A MONEY-GRUBBER,
A REAL SCAM ARTIST
Oh, I'm sorry.
Forgive me.
I'll continue.
Once our Ginza branch
has opened next year,
Tohyama Clinic plans to expand nationwide,
with new branches in Sapporo,
Kyoto, and Fukuoka by the year 2030.
Any questions or concerns, people?
Well…
Forgive me, but I thought
you wanted to keep the practice small.
Not to mention,
has the chairman approved of this?
His approval doesn't matter.
I run this clinic, not him.
Turning a plastic surgery clinic
into a chain is a ridiculous concept.
Do you know why?
It's because a chain could never guarantee
a Hand-of-God-level quality
that can be adapted
for each customer's individual needs.
How can you provide elite service
if you have to employ
whatever mediocre doctors
you can get your hands on?
Of course, I plan to hear out
any concerns the chairman might have.
However, I've decided
that allowing him too much influence
would only limit
the Tohyama Clinic's potential growth.
The concept of beauty
has evolved significantly
since the chairman
was actively practicing as a surgeon.
This clinic
has to adapt or be left behind.
Cosmetic surgery
is the pinnacle of medicine.
The reason
is because we not only treat our patients,
we also increase their social value.
This can only be done
by an exceptional surgeon
with a talent that's one-of-a-kind.
I speak of myself.
The days of plastic surgery
being seen as a novelty are over.
Pretty soon, a visit to a cosmetic surgeon
will be just as ordinary
as a trip to the dentist.
It's only a matter of time.
The plastic surgery industry
is rife with charlatans.
I find this to be… truly disturbing.
SUCCESSOR OF THE HAND OF GOD
In the name of the Tohyama Surgery Clinic,
I promise to unmask these medical frauds
and take them down.
YOU GOT ANY PROOF, MS. COMPLAINER?
YOU KNOW YOU COULD GET ARRESTED FOR THIS?
I HAVE A LAWYER TOO, YOU KNOW?
SHUT UP, FOOLS.
Director, about Dr. Numata.
This was published today.
It's an interview with Kana's mother.
In the article,
she defends Dr. Numata's response.
The nursing staff would like
to make a suggestion.
Maybe the time has come
for Dr. Numata to use her real name?
Using an alias feels
like we're deceiving our patients.
No. It's way too soon for that.
And we don't even know
how many people read this magazine.
Numata, are you committed
to working as a plastic surgeon?
I would also like to hear Numata's answer.
Are you prepared
to use your medical skills
to change people's appearances?
The truth is that…
I'd prefer to work
under my name.
-I'm with you.
-Director.
I understand your concerns, Dr. Rui.
I don't want any blowback on us either.
I'll have our PR department investigate
whether or not the heat
against Dr. Numata has subsided.
I'll make my decision
after seeing the results.
'Kay.
TAKERU NUMATA
CALL ME BACK NOW!
What?
MACKY, TAKASHI, HOME
MISSED CALLS
What the…
TAKERU NUMATA
MISSED CALL ONE HOUR AGO
-Has the time been confirmed?
-Not yet. We're on standby.
-Hey.
-What the hell happened?
She was drinking this morning.
She fell and hit her head.
What did the doctor say?
A nurse said
she was gonna be taken into the ICU.
-Did they really say the ICU?
-Yeah.
Tojo, what's going on?
She suffered a severe contusion,
and she's now having seizures.
-We'll do our best.
-I appreciate it.
Wait, so what is it?
I thought Mom had cirrhosis.
Dr. Rui.
Are you ready for the next patient yet?
Mm, give me another two minutes.
Why do I have to be the one
to pick up Numata's slack?
She has a family emergency.
Nothing to be done.
By the way,
have you seen the recent blacklist?
The blacklist?
All the names of patients
who've filed complaints.
They published their real names?
Yes.
Oh, this one here was a total psycho.
The second she walked in,
she started yelling at the staff,
and even hit the doctor. Ooh!
-Whoa. Hey, can I take a picture?
-Sure.
She then claimed
the whole experience traumatized her,
and she refused to pay for the treatment.
Turns out all her claims
were made up entirely.
-Talk about a pain in the ass.
-Mm.
We should have done more
to stop her from drinking.
Should've tied her to a chair.
She would have found a way
to keep on drinking.
50% SURVIVAL RATE
Seriously?
Here's the dermatologist's diagnosis.
This can be used
as evidence in court, right?
Yes, I don't see why not.
You should have left the clinic
like Mom asked you.
-What?
-I warned you, didn't I?
Takeru, Fumi was only trying
to get rid of our debt.
Mom was stressed out 'cause of it.
SCULPTING THE PAST
How was your day at school?
-Very good.
-What'd you do?
Played with my friends. I played outside.
Played some football. It was fun.
You did a lot of playing.
Did you do anything else today?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
I GOT THE DIAGNOSIS! NOW I CAN GO AFTER
THE DOCTOR AND SEND HIM TO HELL.
Uh, math. All that stuff.
Ms. Yuriko Sakashita,
who caught the public eye
after undergoing
a full-body surgical transformation,
despite having terminal cancer,
is reported
to have passed away last night.
She was 75.
The procedure was filmed
for a documentary,
which includes an interview
from her surgeon, Dr. Rin Tohyama
at the Tohyama Cosmetic Surgery Clinic.
According to her family, Ms. Sakashita
professed her sincerest gratitude to you
just moments before she passed away.
It was because of Ms. Yuriko's courage
that I was able to deliver such results.
This was all possible because of her.
-I suppose it runs in the family.
-We've received comments from viewers.
I've heard
this documentary she was filming
is being adapted into a drama.
What could have been
such a publicity stunt
was instead
turned into a pretty moving story.
Worthy of the Hand of God.
…must have been so encouraging to…
By the way, looks like the Ginza property
we were interested in
was snatched up by someone else.
Watching Ms. Yuriko…
The realtor just called to say that.
Hmm. That's unfortunate.
That location was perfect.
Maybe there's room to negotiate?
Not sure.
They're in the same business as us.
Well,
all the more reason to try to get it.
This case…
Who is it?
…was inspiring for me too.
Because of her resiliency.
Are you sure
you don't wanna unmask these frauds
once and for all?
Oh, Elsa. Are you healed already?
Still swollen,
but no one will notice in this lighting.
You're right.
At this point,
you're indistinguishable from the poster.
I got so tired of the filter accusations.
Hi, I'm Elsa.
Wait. Yama, is that you?
I haven't seen you in ages.
I'm sorry.
I hear you've been requesting me.
You were gone for so long,
I was worried you'd quit.
Wow, you're lovelier than ever.
Thanks.
Oh. What's this?
Happy birthday, Elsa.
Huh?
Please enjoy this premium champagne
and this cake
courtesy of Ms. Elsa's wonderful client.
What? You really did this?
Oh, that's so nice!
Happy birthday.
Oh, thank you. This is wonderful, wow.
Look at all this. Thank you so much.
Happy birthday to you
-She made it through.
-Thank you.
Oh, wow. Thank goodness.
Thank you, Doctor.
Is my mom awake?
Not yet.
She's asleep from the anesthesia still.
I think it's best
to wait until tomorrow to see her.
Before you go, a word?
Mm-hmm.
Must bring back memories, huh?
First time this room has been used
by both parent and child.
How did it go?
She was bleeding heavily.
It was worse than I thought.
I see.
Even if she does wake up,
there is a high chance
that she'll be left
with significant cognitive impairment.
Mm.
Even so,
she'll keep causing us trouble
for a long time still.
Four clinics at the same time. Four!
That means there's openings
for all of us to be director.
But there's four clinics and three of us,
so that leaves one spot open.
Numata?
No, no way. Not a chance.
She'd never get it.
Sorry to have kept you all waiting.
-Hey, everyone.
-Hi.
We were all ready to head out
when a pretty nasty case walked in.
Nasty?
Ah, it was someone from the blacklist.
-Really?
-Yeah, same name and same face.
That's right.
Dr. Rui, you're definitely gonna want
to refuse her service.
Oh no! Why do I have to deal with her?
That's the director's job, isn't it?
Well, the director has a special
VIP client tomorrow at the clinic.
-Mm.
-Will you all have the table d'hôte too?
Oh.
Oh. Don't worry.
I've got the best weight-loss drug
on the market.
-Oh, well, in that case, let's eat!
-Yeah, let's eat!
I GOT THE DIAGNOSIS!
LOOKING FORWARD TO UPDATES.
NICE FORGERY. HOW CHILDISH OF YOU.
Who do they think they are?
OF COURSE IT'S NOT FABRICATED.
THAT CLINIC IS DONE FOR
AND SO ARE YOU, STOOGE.
-Yay! I win!
-One more time, Mommy!
Mommy can't, sweetheart.
She'll be late to the club.
-I've gotta go.
-Please! Can we play again?
Please, Mom?
Oh, fine. Just one more time, okay?
Yes!
Anyway, you know
that Mommy always wins, don't I?
This time, I'm gonna win for sure.
How many times have I heard you say that?
Okay, hurry. Let's go!
Mom.
Are you awake?
I'm in trouble.
What's wrong?
Can I…
borrow your phone?
My Fumi,
she must be so worried.
But, Mom.
Mom, it's me.
Fumi's only
in fourth grade.
She's…
Mm.
-…home alone…
-Don't worry.
-I'm sure she's fine.
-…instead of here.
It'll be fine.
-Your phone.
-It's okay.
Can I use it?
Can you tell me your name?
She has memory loss?
Yeah, I'm afraid she does,
but it's common
after a subarachnoid hemorrhage.
When's your birthday?
Though the memory
usually comes back with rehab.
I see.
October 4th.
Do you know where you are?
Mom, it's me.
Takeru.
A specialist is going to treat
her memory loss.
Okay? Don't worry.
We should go. Hmm?
I gotta go to work.
Look after her.
Doctor, I've uploaded
today's intake forms.
DR. TANUMA
Great, thanks.
Good morning.
-Morning.
-I'm sorry about your mother.
Thanks. She's out of the woods.
Oh. I hear you'll be handling
the counseling sessions today.
A word of advice.
Don't start the conversation with a no.
You have a tendency to do that.
And smile, okay?
Yeah.
Come in.
Excuse me, Dr. Tanuma,
your patient has arrived.
I'm Dr. Tanuma. It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
You can place your belongings here.
-Governor, welcome to my clinic.
-We've been expecting you.
Dr. Rin, it's been a while.
So tell me, Ms. Itai,
what would you like to focus on?
Uh, the buccal fat under my cheekbones.
It's starting to sag,
and I'd like to fix it.
I don't like my philtrum very much either.
I think it's too long.
I know it's not that huge of an issue,
I guess,
but I think that maybe
lifting the cheekbones here
will make my philtrum look a lot shorter.
Okay.
A Global Beauty Hub?
Yes.
Plastic surgery is booming in popularity,
wouldn't you say?
Japanese doctors
are renowned for their skill.
So, I want to promote the idea
of Tokyo as the world capital of beauty.
That's an amazing idea.
So, is this for the upcoming election?
Yes. I think it'll become
a major campaign talking point.
That will certainly appeal
to the female vote.
And I would like
the face of this new campaign to be
my favorite doctor in the entire industry.
Okay?
What?
You willing to help us out?
Of course I will.
I'll be more than happy to help you.
Uh, do you mind if I ask you a question?
Of course.
Thanks.
Um, I see that you had surgery
on your upper lip not long ago, right?
Oh.
No, I've been going to a new dentist,
but the guy has no idea
how to properly inject Novocain.
So the last surgery you had was...
I think it was over a year ago.
Posterior liposuction.
Mm.
Um, in my professional opinion, Ms. Itai,
you've had
a rather large number of surgeries.
And as a result,
the overall balance of your face
has altered.
Oh, okay.
We could shorten your philtrum,
but it might upset the balance
now that your chin--
But the balance is off right now.
That's the problem.
But before you shorten your philtrum--
I'm the one
who has to live with this face, not you.
I know better than you what my face needs.
Okay.
You're right.
Well, the office
will be in touch with details.
Great.
I will do everything I can.
Excited to help.
Sounds great.
So can you fill in Chairman Tohyama
about everything?
Sorry?
Well, can't begin
without our Hand of God, can we?
Both father and daughter
will be the faces of our campaign.
Yes. I'll fill him in on everything.
-Yes, please do.
-Yes.
Great.
Great seeing you.
I'm Denno. I'm the chief counselor.
If you don't mind, let's discuss payment.
Doctor, I'll take it from here.
Oh.
Excuse me.
Well then, shall we see?
Uh, right. Why don't I walk you through
the next steps, then?
DAD
Director, do you have a minute?
Bad news. That patient we just talked to…
Turns out she's on the blacklist.
I'm so sorry. I should have checked
when she booked.
Has her surgery already been scheduled?
-Yes, in two days.
-You gotta be kidding.
I know this isn't really my place to say,
but this patient is still recovering
from her last surgery.
-What?
-That's not right.
Yeah, but I thought--
This is going too far now.
Think about it, Numata.
She's filed complaints
at multiple clinics.
I think she has body dysmorphia
or even an addiction to plastic surgery.
Has she paid in full?
She applied for a loan,
but didn't qualify.
But she insists she can find the cash
to pay upfront if she has to.
Look, I'll call her
and talk to her about it.
Yes?
Good morning. Am I speaking to Ms. Itai?
This is Tanuma
calling from the Tohyama Clinic.
Do you have a moment to chat?
I'm at work, so make it quick.
Yes, yes, of course.
Uh, I'd like to talk to you
about your loan application.
It looks like it wasn't approved,
so according to the clinic's policy--
I said I'd pay cash
if the loan didn't go through.
Right.
But the thing is, according to our policy,
we can't approve surgery for patients
whose loan applications are denied.
What? That's ridiculous.
I have never heard of that.
Do you make everyone who wants to pay cash
apply for a loan?
N… No, we don't, but in your case--
Are you denying me treatment?
I'm recording this call, you know.
I'll sue you.
Um, Ms. Itai,
I might be overstepping here,
but would you come in
for another counseling session?
-Because last time--
-I've got work. I can't talk.
Wait, Ms. Itai, don't go yet--
Damn it!
Shit!
I thought I made myself clear.
You were supposed to get rid of her
for good.
I know, but Ms. Itai won't listen to me.
There's no benefit for our clinic
in doing surgery on someone like her.
You need to take this more seriously.
This is not good for us.
Is that… really my responsibility?
Of course it is.
Proper communication with patients
is one of the most important parts
of being a surgeon.
If you don't get that,
then I definitely can't allow you
to work under your real name.
Okay, I'll speak with her.
-Takashina.
-Yes?
Look into this person for me.
All right.
Ah. Thanks again for seeing me today.
Of course. And thank you as well.
So, about your Beauty Hub project.
I just heard back from the chairman.
Excellent.
What did he say?
He regretfully declined.
But he sends his sincerest apologies.
He's confident I can handle it on my own.
So now this patient
is completely ghosting you.
She won't answer any of my calls.
What am I supposed to do now?
So she's addicted to plastic surgery.
I can see how
the clinic would see her as a liability.
Still, I hope you don't give up on her.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I think I'm also addicted.
Mm, more importantly,
the backlash against you
is gaining traction again.
You mean…
I know. I was surprised to see it too.
Look.
FUMI NUMATA IS STILL A DOCTOR
SHE SWITCHED TO A COSMETIC CLINIC?
Oh, come on.
This again?
I thought the interview
with Kanabun's mother
would calm things down a bit.
Hey, you think someone
could be adding fuel to the fire?
What for? What do you mean?
Girl, I don't know.
-Want me to investigate?
-Can you?
I gotta pay for it?
Sorry, yeah.
I gotta pay for my osteotomy next month.
Mm, fine.
-Let's do it.
-You can count on me.
-An advance?
-I'm sorry.
I wouldn't ask if I didn't really need it.
More plastic surgery?
If you want,
I can get you work at a brothel.
You'll make more money.
But that face wouldn't look so great
in bright lighting, would it?
Here. You ready?
Ah.
There.
Oh. Ah!
Here.
Yeah!
Sorry, Takeru.
-You lose.
-Yeah, you lose!
Suck it, Takeru.
Mom, is your memory back?
Oh.
It's you again.
From the other day.
Would you like… to play cards with us?
Yeah, play with us.
No, thanks.
-Come on, join us!
-Why?
-I'm good.
-The more the merrier, right?
-Right.
-Tell her.
I'll deal. Here we go.
Takeru?
Yeah, just one more time.
What's going on with Mom?
Oh. Apparently, she once dated someone
who looks exactly like Macky.
Really?
Isn't that right, Ms. Taeko?
Mmm.
I guess I look like someone
she knew in school.
Love at first sight.
Right?
That's right.
Hang on, stop!
Come on, knock it off, Takeru.
You don't wanna see this.
-Ha!
-Hey!
-Aha!
-Hey, that's no fair!
Ms. Taeko, you're last.
-Better luck next time.
-Right.
-Let's try again.
-Yeah.
You'll win the next one for sure.
-There you are.
-Thank you.
Hey, Yama.
You mean that?
72-HOUR EMERGENCY CONTRACEPTIVE
Yes?
Hi. It's me. This a good time?
Mm-hmm.
Are you coming to Tomoki's game?
'Cause my parents will be there,
and I really don't want another scene
like last time, understood?
But I was…
I did this.
It's my fault.
Hey.
I'm such an idiot. That's why he…
Mom?
That's why he left. It's all my fault.
It's okay, Mom. It's okay. What is it?
He left me with Fumi.
What?
I'm going to his game, you hear me?
I've been looking forward to this
for so long.
And I promised Tomo that I would be there!
I have to be there.
He doesn't remember
you making that promise.
I'm allowed to see him!
I have visitation rights, you know!
I don't care what your parents think.
It's none of their business!
If you try to stop me from seeing my son,
I'll call my lawyer!
It's my fault.
-It's all my fault.
-Mm. Mom.
Please forgive me, Fumi.
It's okay. You're okay.
-I'm so sorry.
-It's okay.
Hey, Mom.
You're fine.
I need to ask a favor of you.
Mm-hmm. What is it?
I really need some alcohol.
I'm sorry, no.
-If you drink again, you'll die.
-I need it.
-No, I'm sorry.
-I can't take it anymore.
I can get you a glass of water.
Just have some water, take a breath.
-Okay?
-Fine.
-I'll get some myself.
-No, Mom. Stop.
Mom, calm down.
Mom, stop! You'll pull out your IV!
-Let me go!
-Mom! Mom, calm down!
Just stop!
Calm down. It's okay. Relax, it's okay.
It's okay.
Just breathe, Mom.
It's okay. Just breathe.
It's gonna be okay.
Please.
Just breathe.
SEE A PSYCHIATRIST BEFORE A SURGEON
JUST BAN HER ALREADY.
YOU'RE AN EYESORE, OLD WOMAN, SCREW OFF
SHUT UP, PLASTIC SURGERY MONSTERS
I'LL KILL YOU, UGLY FREAKS
BAN HER FROM HERE TOO
SHE HAS NOWHERE ELSE TO BE. PATHETIC.
WHO CARES ABOUT HER?
I'M OBSESSED WITH NUMATA
ANYONE KNOW ANYTHING?
#FIND_FUMI_NUMATA
THE BEST PLACE TO HIDE A LEAF IS A FOREST
I LIKE HER FACE.
SHE HAS A CRINGEY FAN LOL.
Numata?
I'm Dr. Tanuma.
Hi. Oh, thanks.
Heard you had a rough night.
Well, she's still an alcoholic.
-I'm surprised though.
-Look at this view.
I never thought you'd be
so committed to caring for your mother.
I've only ever heard you
complain about her.
You know…
I always thought she hated me
my whole life.
She couldn't even bring herself
to hold my hand.
She'd say things like,
"If a hostess smells like kids,
her career is over."
For real?
She never seemed
like such a toxic parent though.
As a kid,
it was a pretty hurtful thing to hear.
Still though.
Look at you now,
still looking out for her after all that.
I had to look out for Takeru.
Besides,
yeah, she may be flawed,
but she's the only
actual relative I've got.
While I'm here,
can I ask you a question?
Yeah?
Who's that guy? There?
Him?
That's right.
That's Macky.
He's
a moocher.
-A moocher?
-That's right.
-He mooches off you?
-Yeah.
He lives with you?
He doesn't have anywhere to go.
Although, I guess he did kind of move in.
Mm.
-What now?
-Mm-mm.
What?
Hello.
-How can I assist you?
-Is Dr. Tanuma in?
I need to see her.
-Uh…
-Did you hear me?
Go get Dr. Tanuma.
Excuse me, Director.
You're urgently needed up front.
Get Tanuma right now!
Thank you for waiting.
I'm Dr. Tohyama, the director.
I'm very sorry,
but Dr. Tanuma is off today.
She has a family matter to attend to.
You mean Numata, right?
What?
Fumi Numata.
That's her.
Hmm.
I guess, um,
I can see a resemblance to Dr. Tanuma.
Don't treat me like a kid.
Do you think it's okay for someone
like her to work under an alias?
Isn't that a violation
of the Medical Practitioners' Act?
What are you getting at?
Nothing.
All I want
is for her to do my surgery tomorrow
like we'd discussed.
So make sure she's here on time.
You tell her no more excuses.
She has to do my surgery tomorrow. Got it?
Oh. Fumi, you're back.
For my laundry.
Oh.
-Hey, Takashi.
-Yeah?
Uh…
It's about my…
How do I say this?
Hmm?
My real father.
Do you know anything about him?
Uh…
Mom never told me
anything at all about him.
I don't even know if he's alive or dead.
Oh.
Well, to be honest, I don't know either.
If I ask about him, she gets mad.
-I see.
-Hmm.
-Mind if I use an ashtray?
-Go ahead.
But from what I do know,
she was really hurt by him.
-Huh?
-I'm not gonna lie.
I was worried
that even after all these years,
she still wasn't over it.
Maybe that's why
she ended up an alcoholic.
-Good work.
-Thank you so much.
-This way to the dressing room.
-Thank you.
Nice job.
-Great work. Thank you so much.
-No, thank you.
Amazing job.
Hey, well done.
Hi, Dad, good morning.
Hey, so…
My team needed me for a meeting,
so I'm back in Japan.
I see.
Dad, you should have told me sooner.
Well, I have to fly right back tomorrow.
But I called you
because I wanted to talk to you
about Tokyo's Global Beauty Hub project.
I've decided to join the campaign.
I've been wanting to speak out
about the rise of chains
in the plastic surgery industry.
Well, this is the perfect opportunity
to do so.
Oh!
Well, that's great.
I was actually just about to call you
to discuss all that.
Don't worry.
I know what's on your mind, Rin.
No need to tell me.
I'm very much aware of how you feel.
Dr. Rin, great job today.
Do you have a second?
A new project already?
Yes.
The show had a resurgence in popularity
ever since Ms. Yuriko died.
So the network is insisting that
we jump right on another program with you.
Here's our pitch.
BEAUTY REVOLUTION
REIWA EDITION
Are you serious?
Can you let us know
if we can aim for an October release?
DREAM COLLAB FOR THE HANDS OF GOD!
The chairman's doing it?
Well, of course.
He's the most popular part of it.
Well, I mean, with the two of you both
acting as the Hand of God,
just think of the impact in our ratings.
So?
I'm sorry.
My schedule is already completely full,
I'm afraid.
There's no time.
Takashina.
We need… to make a stop.
All right. Where would you like to go?
I'm going to see Dad.
I'm not letting him
push me around anymore.
SNACK BAR ITTENBARI
TOHYAMA CLINIC
Hello?
I'm calling about Ms. Itai.
I've decided
to cancel her surgery tomorrow.
Well, she isn't going to like that.
My plan is to offer her a cash settlement
in exchange for her silence.
So you're hoping
you can just buy her off, huh?
You're the reason
we're in this mess in the first place.
I decided that she's too risky of a client
for us to take on.
If our only concern was a complaint,
that would be perfectly manageable.
However, she has a history
with the police.
The cops?
She went through
a nasty divorce a few years ago.
Seems she filed for custody of her son,
but lost her case in court.
She couldn't let the matter go
and took it upon herself to harass those
who were involved in the case.
I see.
She has also figured out
who you really are, Dr. Numata.
Has she really?
If we don't stop her now,
she'll use this information as leverage.
The clinic is at a critical crossroad.
We can't afford another scandal.
I'll handle this.
I'll talk to her tomorrow.
Oh, and according to our PR department,
the backlash against you
is even more rampant than ever.
So working under your real name
might be a little bit tricky.
Here.
And there.
Takeru. Visiting hours are over.
Why do you get to stay over?
-What?
-I wanna stay.
Can I have many visitors overnight?
One person.
Only one is allowed to stay at a time.
Ask that Dr. Tojo.
He's obsessed with you.
He'll let us both stay.
Dr. Tojo?
-Ah!
-Come on. Stop that.
Come on, it's obvious.
Okay, you can stay.
Lights off.
Hey, come closer.
You don't have to
push the beds that close.
Good night, Ms. Taeko.
Good night.
Uh, if I may…
Hmm?
Isn't your mom…
worried about where you two are?
What?
That's a good question.
She's not really that type of person.
Mm.
Oh, I see.
What's she like?
Huh?
Hey, tell me.
Tell me something about her.
Well,
to be honest…
I hate her more than anyone in the world.
What?
Our mom,
she was a hostess like you, Ms. Taeko.
She was always drunk.
Had tons of lovers.
She would always
put her own needs before anyone else's,
including her kids.
Yeah.
Now, it seems that…
Seems that what?
I'm finally aware that…
life wasn't easy for her.
I'll admit
I've been avoiding talking to her
about how she hurt me.
And now…
I feel like I should have
just listened to her.
I should have asked her to tell me
what she went through.
But…
I missed my chance.
That's not true.
If you're this aware of your feelings…
and I think your mother is too…
and she's lucky to have you.
Hmm.
It's okay.
It's gonna be okay. It's fine.
Someday…
you'll understand each other.
I'm not… I'm not ready to see him.
No, I can't! No!
No! Tomo can't see me like this!
Yes, Tohyama speaking.
Hello, sorry to call so late.
This is Hamaguchi, the TV director.
Um, I just wanted to talk about
the new project.
Dr. Rin has declined.
I see. That's too bad.
In fact, I was very much looking forward
to watching her in action.
Same.
Well, it seems she's really set
on appearing on her own.
I'm very sorry.
We reached out to you, assuming
she'd want a collaboration, but…
Please wait in here for the doctor.
I'll leave it to you, Doctor, to decide
what the final settlement will be.
Excuse me, Director. A moment?
Yes, what is it?
Sorry for interrupting.
It's about Ms. Itai.
I'd like… to take this one on myself.
Why?
Don't you need to scrub up?
Isn't the surgery soon?
Before we proceed, the director would like
to have a word with you.
I don't believe that a cash settlement
will satisfy her.
She's unwell.
She could have surgery after surgery.
She will never be satisfied.
Exactly.
Ideally,
you should have talked to her
about this much earlier.
So I
wanna make sure I understand.
I wanna know
what she's actually struggling with.
I wanna hear her out.
As a doctor.
You asked me once if I felt ready.
Ready to support our patients
who want to change their appearance.
I need to do this.
To hear her out.
Please, Director.
Excuse me.
Director.
The chairman is out front.
You want to get surgery?
I know it's very sudden,
but I'd like you to do it.
What made you want this now?
Well, I looked
for a suitable doctor in Dubai,
but I just couldn't find one.
It's a fairly big surgery.
So I figured, why not ask
the most trustworthy doctor.
What kind of surgery?
Do you remember Ms. Yuriko?
I'd like the same procedure.
I'd like a facelift.
You okay?
Unfortunately, our anesthesiologist
isn't in today, so--
I've already reached out to Taki.
He's on his way.
Oh, one other thing.
I'd like to film the surgery
and air it on my channel.
The publicity will be good
for the Global Beauty Hub.
I'd like to apologize
for lying about my identity.
DR. TANUMA
If
you're willing
to give me a second chance, Ms. Itai,
I swear I'll do my best.
How can I trust anything you have to say?
You can't.
But I would still like to help you
however I can.
I will hear you out…
as a surgeon and without any judgment,
until you walk out of here
totally satisfied.
Tell me.
Can I really trust you?
What is it?
I heard a talented doctor
joined us recently.
Ms. Tanuma.
You've got great fingers for surgery.
If only we were all so lucky.
Director.
It's okay.
Lights.
-Administering anesthesia.
-Right.
-We'll begin the lip lift.
-Anesthesia.
-Here.
Director, the anesthesia
has been administered.
Scalpel.
Yes.
Director, should we wait
until Dr. Numata is finished?
Dr. Numata, a moment?
-Okay. Continue hemostasis.
-Understood.
-Close the door.
-Yes.
Excuse me.
I understand.
-New gauze.
-Yes.
It's okay.
All right.
-Let's begin.
-Okay.
Here we go. Hold on tight!
It's like we're off to the races!
So what do you think of
my driving skills, huh?
You win best driver ever!
Can you imagine
if they actually end up together?
Don't be so weird.
It's all so weird.
Hmm?
She lost her memories,
but she's still Mom.
You're being so nice to her.
Well, yeah. Doctors always try to be nice.
You know,
this whole situation might not be so bad.
How so?
When you think about it,
we'd all be happier if we could forget.
DIRECTOR
Hello.
Hi! It's nice to finally meet you.
I've heard so much.
Come in.
Oh, thank you.
Rin.
Whoa!
Thank you for coming all this way.
It's my pleasure.
Since we've both made it out
of a tough situation,
I thought we could celebrate
with a home-cooked meal.
We still don't know
how Ms. Itai will feel.
We haven't gotten any complaints yet,
which leads me to think
she was satisfied with her surgery.
I hope so.
Wow, your home is so nice.
Thank you.
If you keep working for us for a year,
you could get a place like this.
Just like that, huh?
Would you mind if I look around?
By all means.
Dinner is ready. It'll get cold.
Ah, in that case,
let's save the tour for later.
You never want to annoy
the person who's handling your food.
Ms. Taeko, I'm off.
Good night.
Sleep well.
What?
You're crazy.
Game Boy is in black and white.
No, it's in color.
See? I told you yours was broken.
No way, I swear. I got it for my birthday.
But then why was mine in black and white?
Oh no. Does that mean I'm officially old?
Good lord.
OKURA
URGENT! CAN WE TALK NOW?
Oh. So sorry.
Um, do you mind if I make a call?
Not at all. Use the balcony.
-Thank you so much.
-Of course.
Hello?
I found out who's been adding fuel
to the fire against you online.
I'm listening.
It's some guy named Takashina.
He's from the Tohyama Clinic.
Used to be a detective.
Seems like he's been leaking info on you
to major influencers
and spreading rumors to keep you trending.
But the whole thing is weird
'cause, I mean, you've been working there
for a while now, right?
So what exactly is the point of
stirring all of this up against you now?